Not too technical, not too complicated.
Thank you so much, Hila, for the invitation —
and it's really great to meet everyone here.
This looks like an amazing community of people
who genuinely support one another —
you've built something really special here
that truly encourages creativity. That's remarkable.
Can everyone see the screen? Good.
We need to switch to presentation view.
Is the slide visible now?
Great. First of all, there's a link here
for anyone who just joined and missed the messages.
That link gives you ten dollars in credit
to try out the platform.
So — a little about what I'm covering today.
I'm talking about scaling up lookbooks,
editorials, social content, and campaigns
for fashion, e-commerce, and DTC brands.
Also joining me on this call are Daniel Ryan
and Sivan Aharon, who are part of our team.
Sivan made the video
— the video you may have seen — and is
a huge help on the creative side.
Daniel handles the business side.
Feel free to reach out to any of us — our emails are available.
Alright. Let me quickly outline
where we're going today.
Here's roughly the structure:
We'll talk about what traditional photoshoots involve,
how things look today — AI photoshoots
are already happening at major companies.
We'll look at real examples.
We'll explain what brand identity is
and how it translates into AI.
We'll discuss how to apply brand identity in AI,
how to work as a creative director
inside the system,
and how to use references from the real world.
Then we'll get into prompt editing and refinement —
making sure you consistently get strong output
with fewer bugs and artifacts.
After that, how to turn that work into templates
so you can run shoots faster —
that's the core of the "scale up" I mentioned.
How to use the Describe tool to bring
existing client assets into the AI world.
How to deliver a digital product to a client.
What we're building at Astria is a system that enables
a real dialogue between creative professionals and brands.
We don't just deliver images — and then all the work is wasted.
We deliver a digital product: a template.
Finally, the brand or the creative runs the looks themselves.
And then a few closing thoughts.
That's the structure. So let me start with
a quick overview — what do I mean when I say
"AI photoshoot"? I mean everything that involves
the logistics of a traditional shoot:
coordinating models,
locations, shipping all the inventory —
making sure product arrives
from production to the shoot day.
Stylists, makeup, hair —
all of that logistics
ultimately exists to serve the brand's DNA.
The whole photoshoot is there to convey
the brand identity,
and we need to somehow implement and communicate that.
I want to step back for a moment to what Hila said.
I also come from a technical background — machine learning, coding —
and my world has changed a lot too.
Everyone codes in Claude now.
I've largely stopped writing code myself.
I've moved more toward product thinking —
directing at a higher level. That doesn't mean
I don't need to understand what's happening underneath.
The same applies here. Creative professionals,
photographers — they're absolutely not being replaced.
But you still need to guide the system.
You need to know how to work with a brand,
understand its DNA, apply it, and direct the AI.
Without that, there's no context —
and you can't produce anything distinctive.
Part of not looking like AI
is creating differentiation —
a very distinctive aesthetic.
We'll talk about that.
So — what kinds of brands are we talking about?
Brands in the e-commerce space,
DTC — direct to consumer —
brands selling directly to consumers
without physical retail,
as well as retailers with stores.
The verticals relevant to today's session
are fashion and apparel —
shirts, jackets, pants, dresses, wedding dresses,
footwear,
outdoor and trekking gear, bags, handbags,
jewelry — and when I say jewelry
I mean independent jewelers more than diamond companies.
Also eyewear.
Eyewear companies have a strong DNA
in how they look and present themselves.
This next slide shows that the AI world
is already here and operational.
This is an example of a campaign for Saks —
actually not a campaign, they transformed
their site with the help of Shai Yechezkel,
a photographer who works with us as a real partner.
You're seeing the entire website —
it's all generated
with Shai's work. He brought the creative eye,
built their model set,
built the template set,
and then ran all the looks
to produce the full collection.
They're now
on their second collection — and everything is generated.
Another example: Nine West,
already using AI for
in-store signage, back-of-checkout displays,
and billboards.
Then there's Ronit Alkabetz — a Paris-based
elite designer working with AI.
All of this was done in Astria.
And of course there are also
the big players — Mango, H&M, Zara —
they're all working in AI,
producing both campaigns and lookbooks.
The world is already there de facto.
What remains is to direct it well,
scale it up, and do it precisely.
So let's talk about brand identity
and how to create something truly special.
We're looking at a demo we built for a fictitious Zara.
This was created by Sivan Aharon,
who's part of this community,
and you can see how there's a set of templates
for different types of garments —
pants, shoes, shirts,
dresses, jackets,
heels. Each one speaks a different language
and requires different templates
and different refinements.
You can see that everything here is clickable —
there's a set of studio images,
and Zara in particular has moved
all of their lookbooks toward outdoor photography,
which is why we see those options here.
What we're really showing is how we implement
a brand's visual language in AI —
how this speaks in the language of Zara.
Let me show a few more examples.
A sportswear brand modeled more around Adidas.
You can see the slightly more intense expressions,
the athletic energy. Here too
there's a set of templates
that brands can pick up and use.
We've already had companies that took these templates
off the shelf and said:
"This is beautiful, but it's not my brand. It's not me."
And that's exactly the important thing to recognize
when working with brands.
You need to ask: who is the target audience?
What's their age range?
What are the client's existing materials?
What brief do they give you?
How should the models look?
Short hair? Gel?
I don't come from this world,
so forgive me
for not knowing all the precise terminology —
but that's exactly the point.
This is why it matters.
Here's another example —
a basics brand modeled more
around Uniqlo, similar to brands like
Fox — hoodies, that kind of thing.
You can see there are several distinct brand types here,
all illustrating this idea of brand identity.
Each brand has its own background color,
its own hex values, its own expressions,
its own set of models
that define it — so when you see it you say,
"That's that brand.
That look, that feel, it's right for that age group,
that type of person,
that atmosphere."
So how do we actually build this in Astria,
and how did we decide
to translate it into a product?
Tali, I think you're not on mute.
So at Astria there's a core concept
of templatization — templates.
We take prompts, group them together,
and turn them into a single template.
Those who know Astria from before —
this used to be called a pack.
We're moving away from that term.
Today we call it a template.
You can see here the example of the template
I started showing earlier.
This is the idea behind
what we want to deliver to the brand.
We want to create a workspace for them.
Workspaces are up here at the top.
We open one workspace per brand
to keep clients separate.
Clients also sit within the workspace —
they're added to the workspace,
they put in their credit card,
and generations are charged to the client.
They can see all materials.
This is part of what matters to clients —
it gives them confidence,
because once the collection or campaign is done,
their assets keep living and breathing.
They receive templates they can continue
to develop and refine over time,
growing them and keeping up with trends.
So here you can see how you can simply take
a different dress and run the same templates
to get similar images.
In a lookbook that's completely fine —
most brands want a consistent-looking lookbook.
Some want very precise uniformity,
others want some variation.
And that's one of those layers
you can control through the right prompt —
either high precision or, conversely,
allowing some randomness.
There's also a feature called Brief
which allows you to generate variety.
Here's the key point — and I've said it once
but I want to say it from a different angle:
brands generally need help.
They cannot make this transition alone.
They don't understand AI, they don't know
how to write prompts, they don't know
what nano banana is. A lot of the time
they want to hand things off
and have someone help them — send over the looks,
the items, and get assistance.
That's exactly why the templatization concept exists.
Someone needs to come in and help them
make that transition. The platform
enables the abstraction and the collaboration.
Six months ago it was LoRA with Flux.
Then it was nano banana Gemini 2.5.
Today it's nano banana 2.
The brand doesn't care and doesn't want to know.
And it doesn't end with building the templates.
If today it's nano banana 2,
in two months they'll need help
upgrading to nano banana 3, to seed dream
and seed dance 2. If today they need still images,
tomorrow they'll need video,
the day after — multi-format.
The technology keeps evolving.
Think about how it was predicted that the vacuum cleaner
would replace the cleaner's job.
It didn't — the standard just went up.
Or that computers and 3D would replace animators.
They didn't — there are just far more films
being made, and the bar rose.
The same is true here. There's a need to produce
far more media,
more variety, more differentiation,
and I think this technology
is in many ways, as they say in English,
leveling the playing field.
It allows players who couldn't previously produce
high-quality content
to now do so.
So — coming back to the practical side.
We're looking at a template the brand receives.
Someone in the studio can simply click Upload,
upload a photo from a hanger and run it,
and receive a lookbook with a single click —
without having to define anything.
The framework was already defined for them —
the models, everything.
They can of course override things.
Some of Astria's features allow for variation —
say we want to shift the mood slightly,
or add some accessory and say,
"This time she's sitting on an armchair," —
that's the Brief concept.
It still runs the entire template
under one coherent idea.
You can change the bag, you can change the model,
but at the core — the product this template is selling
is the dress. And first and foremost,
you can customize the dress.
Beyond that, you can of course run thirty dresses
with a single click
and get all the output at once.
That's the key thing. And how does the brand
see the full collection?
They don't just need one template —
they need a set of templates,
because each garment type behaves differently.
A jacket requires different crops
and different details than shoes,
and different model positioning,
and probably outdoor photography too.
So the brand needs a set of templates,
and they see this through their template page.
They can choose: now I want to run dresses,
now shirts, now boots. That's what the brand sees.
Now let's look at how we actually create
and deliver this.
Now we're getting to the more practical part —
everyone is welcome to open the link from earlier
and try to follow along and work with me in the system.
You're welcome to open a Workspace —
and try to work in a way
where all your materials are organized
under one theme.
I'd recommend trying it with a real concept —
take a brand you have in mind
that you love, and experiment with something real.
Think about a story — something special.
Try to create a concept that's unique.
You can really go creative —
whether it's a farmers market
or underwater scenes with jellyfish,
I've seen some beautiful things like that.
So you can open this — there's a link here
to the Generative tab. We've tried to really simplify Astria.
For those who've used Astria before,
I know it might look different.
That's fine — it's just the one link.
I shared it in chat.
That's how you also get the ten dollars.
Let me open a Workspace as well —
Just a moment, let everyone connect.
Yes.
OK.
[In response to a question about login:]
Everyone click Generate in the top right.
Can you see where he's clicking?
Log in first — log in.
Everyone needs to log in first.
Yes, just sign in with your Google account or whatever works.
Then click Generate.
OK.
Did everyone click? Is everyone good?
Fine, we're waiting. Everything's fine.
Yes.
[In response to a question about LoRA:]
Yes, absolutely — it's still available.
You can still go into the old menu —
yes —
which used to be called fine-tuning.
It's now called References — and you can still create LoRA
there. Absolutely still possible.
OK so — just for anyone watching the recording —
we're supposed to go to the Generative tab and there's
a —
Yes, yes, we'll do that, we'll do that.
Let's meet back in about fifteen minutes, sound good?
Sure. I'm not stopping the recording —
I'm just getting organized.
I've already got everything queued up and ready.
[In response to a question about Pack Shot:]
Yes — which means you can also shoot it with your iPhone.
Right.
If you're a small designer with no Pack Shot —
just a decent iPhone photo —
that's fine. But what you need to understand
is this has nothing to do with
the Astria system itself.
The system runs on technologies like nano banana, Flux,
and others.
What happens is we're showing something to the AI —
I show it this sweater,
I tell it to put it on a model.
I can photograph it on a hanger, on the floor, on a mannequin,
and it will dress a model with it.
But yes — photo quality matters
in terms of how much texture and detail
the AI can see.
If I shoot under my room lighting
with shadows falling across the sweater
and it looks distorted — the AI will struggle
to understand how that sweater should look.
If I photograph it properly — I'd even invest
in some lighting because it's worth it.
It saves me shooting days. I point the light at the sweater,
style it correctly,
and then use it — and the image will be sharper,
textures will be much more visible.
Whether it's a Pack Shot or a regular photo
does change the game.
But even without a professional Pack Shot
it's still possible to create great things.
No — not needed.
[In response to a question about training models per garment:]
If it's a Pack Shot or a regular photo —
that does change the rules of the game.
But even those who can't do professional Pack Shots
can still create output with this.
No, no, no. What he'll teach you
is how to show the item from every angle —
Workspace.
Yes — so it's possible that you didn't select a background,
so just click Pick a Color
and that will give you a uniform color.
Since the technology isn't perfect yet,
it needs you —
because things happen.
Not in this system, but in Midjourney for example —
I want a girl standing in a forest,
and no matter what I do,
it keeps giving me a medium shot.
It doesn't show her feet, no matter what I write —
Wide Shot, describing her shoes.
But if I describe "the girl touching the ground"
— suddenly it gives me the full body shot.
Can everyone see the screen?
So — where we left off:
how to actually create these templates.
I hope everyone is safe and OK.
There's a new button here called Lookbook
which helps us
get started with prompts and begin creating
what we want.
The first step is simply to drag and drop,
or upload, your references.
Let's say we start working with a shirt and pants —
and they happen to be available.
We have a public gallery
of models and
shirts and pants just to make it easy
to demonstrate.
She's asking about the Try tab — what clients see.
The...?
The tab.
She means the Workspace.
Workspace.
In the dropdown at the top
there's an option to work in Workspaces.
If you click there, you can Add a new workspace
and create a workspace scoped
to the organization you're working with.
OK.
No problem — we'll fix that.
But for now,
just —
just go through the Generate window,
which is the same window —
and the button will be added for you.
Click on Generate.
Use the link in the chat — you'll be able
to open a new workspace and then
you'll see that dropdown.
It's just not open to everyone by default.
Can everyone see the Generate window?
Click Generate —
and if you want to see the grid squares,
Yes — click Lookbook.
So —
the Lookbook is essentially a prompt builder
designed to be a bit more visual.
It doesn't replace anything —
it doesn't do anything behind the scenes.
You can actually see the prompt
being built in the background.
Let's take some examples.
The simplest example: take a model's face,
a shirt, jeans.
And I'll even drag in some shoes
— for the demo I'll also add
some shoes I'll search for.
[setting up demo]
She's not registered by the way.
In principle you can also just copy-paste things in.
I don't know who that background noise was —
please put yourself on mute.
[In response to a question about using a pre-built character:]
This isn't a character sheet.
Here it's just the face.
It's best to use just the face,
from the neck up — no clothes.
Yes —
It's just a photo of the model —
no special setup needed.
This is not like what we did before.
Let me give a few tips on references.
First — technically, to upload things
there are a few ways:
click the plus sign here, and a picker opens —
similar to Google Flow —
with an Upload button.
You can also drag directly.
It recognizes the type of item
and adds the thumbnail.
I'll do a copy-paste here.
You can't see my desktop,
but I'll paste the shoes in —
and you'll see it uploads them and adds them.
So now we have:
model, shirt, pants, shoes — that's the basic.
Let's also add a background.
There's a Color Picker here too.
You can't see it right now,
but for those who try — it's very important for brands
that when you open their page,
things are consistent with the same background.
A uniform background is very, very important.
We even have a post-processing step
that works a bit like Photoshop to ensure consistency,
because nano banana doesn't always listen.
If you tell it white background FFF,
it doesn't always do that.
So we have a post-processing step afterward
to help enforce that.
Now — a bit about the technical parameters.
Today the recommended model to work with is nano banana 2.
It's the most accurate and the fastest.
3×4 is how most product pages are built today.
2K is my recommendation —
it's a good balance between cost and quality.
If you're happy with something,
you can consider going up to 4K.
Just note that 4K is very,
very slow — and Google is struggling
to supply enough compute these days.
Sometimes you'll see errors
when we're handling the most requests.
We're constantly working to keep the system
as stable as possible. We have fallbacks,
we pay Google extra just to get enough quota —
and still, sometimes there are overloads.
So my recommendation is —
[In response to a question about model source images:]
Yes — if you upload a character created in Midjourney,
just drag-and-drop into the prompt box and it will work.
No, no, no. Everything is private.
Everything lives under your Workspace
and is private to the people in that Workspace.
Nothing — we've eliminated public galleries.
We understand the privacy concern.
We're removing everything public.
There's no more public feed.
Except for packs or templates
you actively choose to publish.
By default, everything is private.
[In response to a question about the color picker:]
There's a button here called Pick a Color.
It opens a system dialog —
by default it opens in RGB,
but you can click it
and choose a hex value.
And the best approach here —
really go to the brand's website
and sample the hex color directly,
color by color.
You can see the prompt being built
step by step — and there's almost no text here.
I'll generate — and you can see
a prompt is formed, processed —
almost no text at all. Let me explain something:
there's a common assumption that if you write
a complex prompt with extra-realistic faces
that will make all the difference.
That's nice and important —
but I don't think that's where the real value lies.
The value is in the precision of the details —
knowing where to work with the model
even when it's hard to get it
to avoid mistakes.
Knowing to pay attention to the brand's specifics matters.
You only see that after iterations —
after generating and running maybe ten looks,
suddenly realizing:
the shirt needs to be untucked.
It's not a complex prompt.
Just write "untucked shirt."
Or the brand wants different facial expressions —
"change random mimics."
Or write "smiling." Same thing —
if you want to work in the Lookbook,
you can type it right here and it's a bit more visual.
I can type "smiling, untucked shirt."
Now a few more tips on references.
I uploaded a shoe from the side view.
Not recommended — not a great idea.
That's just what I had from the website.
I recommend uploading shoes at 45 degrees —
two shoes, without a person.
For garment references — you can ask the brand
for what's called a flat lay:
on a table, good lighting. You can also use a hanger —
it's generally less ideal but workable.
Depending on the brand and different sensitivities,
this works very, very well.
[In response to a question about Pack Shot vs. on-body:]
It's a question that gets a bit more technical,
but let me explain.
AI models love statistics. They work based on
what's prevalent in popular culture.
If the jeans are standard —
if it's a garment the model has seen before
and was trained on — it'll probably know
how to reproduce it.
Let me give an extreme example from something we saw:
a brand we worked with had a logo that changed.
It had a crest with text on it —
but in an older version the text was at the top.
It's a very well-known brand,
and the models were trained on the entire internet —
they learned the text was on top.
No matter how many times you tried to give it the reference,
it kept generating the old version.
So that's an example of how models work
based on what they learned from the past.
The same applies here. It depends on whether
the garment is unique — or something the model knows well.
And for unique items, there's trial and error.
A lot of the time there's
another layer — whether it's something
you and I can describe and articulate.
The cut, the fit, the length of the dress.
If we can say — below the knee, above the knee,
three-quarter length — then the model can say it too.
If we don't know, neither does it.
Then it might make sense to put it on a mannequin or dress form.
That's more work —
but that's one option. Another option
is to specify it at the generation level —
add detail to that specific garment's generation.
Write "balloon pants" and it comes out perfect.
But that requires an eye that knows —
"I can see this won't come out right,
I know what it needs, I'll fix it." And sometimes
things just need that attention.
More things that help with references
for getting good results.
Your references should be clean.
But there are editing tools —
if you're shooting on a hanger or similar,
there's a wrench icon here
where you can do Remove Background —
remove any messiness from the background.
Crop — to crop the garment precisely
and remove things like other hangers
that were in the background.
There's also an Edit with nano banana tool —
where you can literally say:
"Turn into an iron flat lay" —
and it converts something on a hanger
into a flat lay
that looks cleaner and more polished.
This can sometimes affect accuracy.
Usually it works well.
You need to know how to use these tools
and decide your approach based on
how you decided to photograph the references.
That's broadly it. You could go much deeper,
but that's the general idea.
That is —
[In response to a question about background types:]
We'll get to that shortly.
We started from the Lookbook helper —
the most visual way in — for more special use cases. But —
Here I'm only dealing with a solid color, right?
Of course. Just like you uploaded a shirt,
you can click the picker,
hit Upload, and upload a background image.
Or even better — just describe it.
You can write "on a Parisian
bridge." Let's try it just for fun.
Yes, you really don't need more than that.
No elaborate prompt needed.
I'm a fan of prompts up to about three lines,
maximum around 200 words —
that's great. But the important part
of working with references is the balance
between references and text.
Sometimes it's worth using image references —
for style references for example.
Say the brand sells shoes
but we also need to style pants.
We can decide whether the templates we create
will use image references for pants —
actual photos to upload — in which case
when the brand wants variety they actually need to bring
a different pants reference.
Or we can just write it as text — like "blue chinos" —
something like that.
And then the template is textually flexible
and editable via the brief.
There's a certain playfulness here
you need to learn.
Also note — don't include shoes
if you want a medium shot.
Or if you want jewelry,
don't include the whole outfit —
it can confuse the model.
If you want medium and you give it shoes,
it'll show the whole body.
Watch out for that.
Yes — there's a lot of room for bugs here.
If we want a close-up of the shoes,
but we give it a face,
it'll try to fit the face in somewhere
and create distorted figures —
because it's trying to include both
the face and the shoes
while you've asked for a medium close-up.
Same thing in reverse — if you want
a shirt close-up but give it shoes,
it won't know what to do.
You need to structure your prompts
so these details are consistent — and free of those bugs.
Let's move forward a bit.
So we started with the Lookbook builder —
more visual and simple.
Now for more complex things,
when you want to describe more —
you can go to the prompt box and define things directly.
Let's take an example here.
Here we go.
You can really go to town on the prompts
and add the key words — small in number
but high in impact.
"Diffused lighting," "realistic skin,"
"soft expression" — things like that.
These are what give it the touch
and the things that matter to the brand —
saying: "The expression of my models is serious,
or they're happy, or pleased."
"This is a children's brand,
this is a low-cost brand,
or this is high-end." What exactly does the brand say?
What does it need to convey?
Let me pause for a moment — I want to show
a feature that helps a lot here.
It's called the Describe tool — this button here.
The Describe tool — this button.
Let me explain what's happening here.
I recorded this demo
when I didn't have a specific brand available —
so I used Pinterest.
In principle, the materials we should use
are the client's existing materials — ones they own the rights to.
But in my case I took Pinterest.
What you can do here is take an image,
copy it,
and paste it into the Describe box.
As you can see, the interface
has changed a bit, but there's a "paste from clipboard" option.
What it does is extract the prompt —
similar to what you may have done in Gemini
or similar tools —
and it describes the prompt, and generates the image.
Let's take an example here.
To simplify: you go to Pinterest,
copy an image, come back,
click Describe and paste —
and it basically converts the image into words.
And the key difference from what you'd do in Gemini
is that it listens to the references you already have
and makes sure not to describe those references.
What can happen otherwise
is a conflict between the prompt
and your references.
For example, it writes "wearing a white shirt"
but your reference is a yellow dress —
and then the model doesn't know what to generate.
It sometimes produces
a yellow dress, sometimes a white shirt —
because there's both a shirt reference and a dress reference.
So you need to be very careful
about conflicts between text and references.
That's part of what the Describe tool tries to handle —
it listens to what's already in your references
and removes descriptions of things
that already exist.
That's exactly the example of the shoes
and medium shots we talked about.
You can see — we have a shoe reference
and that conflicts with a medium shot.
Let me show another example — I'll remove the shoes.
In short: you converted an image to words
and it didn't override the clothing
because it knew to adapt to the clothing
that was already there.
So — in the Lookbook builder
we didn't take into account
something here — there are stick figures
that help create pose angles.
This is also worth factoring in. You can see
it's inserting a text variable here
that helps lock in the angle.
And that helps create more consistency
in exactly how the figure is positioned.
Depending on what the brand wants —
in principle you can also
select different angles.
If we want to generate front, back, and side view at once,
there's a dedicated button for that — "Add Front Back" —
and you can see it. For any use case —
if we just want
to test by choosing two models,
I can click the plus, pick two models —
and when I click Generate it will create
both options. It'll generate two prompts —
one with this model and one with the other.
I'll leave that — it's a bit advanced,
and I think there's a bug there right now, sorry.
But the idea with the pose is that you can easily
generate front, back, and side views —
which is the basic thing everyone wants.
[In response to a question about face proportions:]
These kinds of bugs usually happen
from a crop that's too close — like just the face.
I'd recommend using the wrench button
and doing "edit with nano" —
write "shoulders and up"
with no clothing visible.
That's very important —
don't let a shirt show,
otherwise it bleeds into the generations.
If you have a black shirt and try to generate
with a dress, it'll produce
a black shirt with a dress layered on top.
Very important — no clothing.
And also — someone asked earlier:
"I only want a face but don't want
to show body type." That's just in the prompt.
Just write the body type in the prompt.
Just write it alongside. That's the next question.
Where do you write the model-specific prompt?
Just in the prompt — it doesn't matter technically,
it's more to help us
keep organized. We want to create a system
where it's easy to avoid mistakes.
There's a lot of room for mistakes.
People always say "it's not coming out right."
Those are always bugs you can fix —
in text, in prompts, or by improving references.
For example, people often say
"the model isn't tall enough."
OK — write "180 centimeters tall."
That's roughly the level of it.
I'll be running forward in the remaining few minutes.
Ultimately, what we want to arrive at is:
once we're happy with the result,
we turn it into a template.
Turn it into a template by clicking this button here —
and choosing — the word "pack" will disappear from the lexicon
and become "template."
Associate it with
a new pack. You can see that a tag is created here —
and from this point we can deliver this digital product
to the client.
The client can run looks against
these templates.
Again — you need several templates
for different types of items.
That's an example of what a lookbook run actually looks like.
In practice, the client will often deliver
a table specifying the styling:
which shirt with which pants,
with which shoes, with which
necklace, with which earrings —
and perhaps in a certain template
she's leaning against the wall more,
and in another template, one leg to the side —
and all of those looks need to run
against the templates we built.
That's the full workflow from A to Z —
from how the brand sees it, to creating the prompts,
to templatizing and running
looks — either in the brand's studio
or by the creative team.
Depending on the brand and what works.
That's broadly it.
[In response to a question about multiple models:]
Yes — we have models
for things more like campaigns —
so there's no issue at all.
[In response to a question about proportions for jewelry/bags:]
As I said earlier — if you and I
can't describe the proportions,
then neither can the model.
That's where it might actually make sense
to photograph it on a model.
Depending on what we want.
Someone asked about jewelry —
yes, there are examples of jewelry,
examples of eyewear too.
[In response to a question about adding size in cm:]
You can try it. I don't think measurements in centimeters
are necessarily how the model thinks —
we have to consider how the model was trained.
Was it trained on images where centimeter size was written?
Probably not on the internet.
But maybe the word "small" or "tiny"
would help — or "big" — depending on what you're working with.
You can also try centimeters. I'm not sure.
[In response to follow-up about model height vs. dress length:]
Honestly it depends on nano banana
and how much it listens.
Sometimes it works better, sometimes less so.
But in general, if we feel the model
should be taller, we'll try adding keywords —
"180cm" and "tall."
It's not a physics simulation —
it's not 3D rendering.
It listens in a relative way — it knows 180 is taller,
so we'll see some change.
[In response to a question about creating new models:]
Sure, absolutely. I didn't touch on this, but
the basic approach is just to write it
in the prompt box —
"unique Israeli woman with French and
Japanese descent, fair skin,
studio white background, shoulders up."
Or use the Describer — those of you
who don't want to write it manually.
Yes, the Describe tool can work for this too.
But really —
go to Pinterest, find models you love,
put them into the Describer —
or what I do in Midjourney is bring in
a few faces I like as reference images,
blend them, make them a "baby" model,
and bring that here.
[In response to a question about print/pattern accuracy:]
In principle that works great — it works very well.
In cases where it doesn't work well —
you can give a detail view
in addition to the reference —
and that will improve it.
We're also working on a custom model of ours
that will improve detail handling.
Coming back to the avatar / model topic —
once you've created a model
that you're happy with — of course,
if you bring one from Midjourney,
just drag and drop into the prompt box and it'll work.
If you created it in Astria,
there's a menu option here:
Convert to Reference — and then she's added to
the prompt box
and given a name automatically.
[In response to a question about using a real photographed model:]
Yes, you can —
just copy-paste her photo. That's it.
But there are legal considerations —
you need to be really careful.
Right — that's between you and whatever
you've agreed with the model — but
[In response to a question about body changes:]
It can't change her body. If I only input her face —
the system has no idea about her body.
The body needs to be specified in the prompt —
you need to write measurements.
This is not face training — it's different.
If consistency of a specific person is very important —
say you're making a clip for a specific singer —
don't do that through the lookbook system.
That whole scenario is less suited to consistent-character work
where the face is very important.
Though there is a solution for that too —
I'll leave it out of this conversation for now,
it's a bit more complex.
[In response to a question about multiple angles:]
Yes — there's a button in the Lookbook:
Add Front, Back, and Side —
and it generates all three prompts at once —
front, back, and side.
But everything we've talked about,
everything on this screen —
is meant for building templates.
Once we lock that in and we're happy,
our goal is to templatize it,
associate it with a template,
and hand it to the brand so they can run it.
So — the prompt helper is just a very naive builder.
When you get to refinements,
you'll need to add — "in back view
I need the hair off to the side" —
and similar details.
So it's a starting point — not the destination.
[In response to a question about the demo examples:]
Those examples you saw at the start?
Yes — that template is what we build
and deliver to the brand.
Then the brand can simply upload a shirt
and get that same lookbook —
more or less the same look and feel.
That's the goal.
The goal is to nail the background,
the expressions, the model, the hair.
Hair band or slick hair pulled back —
all the things the brand cares about —
to create consistency. And of course that varies
by garment type and requires
very specific keywords.
That's the concept broadly.
I also wanted to show something that was sent to me
this morning — it's a Noyz collection
where all the references were uploaded this morning.
Someone asked about multiple people.
You can really start to see the idea emerging —
a kind of main CRM for the brand.
Once all the items and models are in the system,
you can start producing
campaigns and editorials much more easily —
bring in four models with a consistent
background and scene.
This is the entire new collection —
all done in Astria by Shai Yechezkel.
[In response to "are these real models?"]
No — they're virtual.
That's part of the process —
he worked with the brand, built out
the model characters.
For anyone with children, AI is always preferable
because working with child models
involves so many complications.
Look at that — let me show them the video.
Important.
[In response to a question about pack structure:]
I think the standard is to create
about four models for them.
You want to get those approved by the brand —
give them ten options, they choose four,
and those four tell a consistent story
that conveys
the brand identity.
[In response to follow-up on workflow:]
Exactly. Lock in the prompt,
add it to the pack, and from that point
you can run it —
The pack is accessible here in the menu.
Once she's created a generation — you see the image there.
On the right there's a small menu.
Click on the hamburger icon
and you'll see the word "Pack" — which will soon
become "Templates." Click it and there's a New Pack option.
Click New Pack and it creates
a new template you can always return to —
regardless of what garments you put in,
it will apply what you originally defined:
that model, that background, that lighting.
Yes — this is the template we create
and deliver to the brand.
Then the brand can just swap in another garment —
keep the same angle but
change everything else — same background, model, everything.
The goal is to run this for the brand
who has a hundred items from the manufacturer —
run a hundred shirts and a hundred pairs of pants
in the same angles and same appearance
with four different models.
That's the goal — upload another shirt,
or select thirty shirts at once
and click Generate — and run everything
against the template you built.
[In response to a question about using a pack:]
Go up to My Packs.
My Packs.
Here — My Packs. There's the template I built.
I can now choose a different shirt,
upload a different shirt,
and run the template.
[In response to a question about pack contents:]
Yes — the pack can contain
front, side, back views and a certain atmosphere.
The pack contains a collection of prompts —
as you see in the Zara example:
front, back, side, detail view —
and the variations are random. That is,
if you write "model standing against a white background
leaning on an object" —
the object changes randomly.
If you write "chair," there will be a specific chair,
or it will vary.
It depends on how open your prompt is.
[In response to a question about the video:]
Yes, yes — the video was also done in Astria.
[In response to a question about generating video:]
There's a video button — a simple one —
that gives you all available models,
and there's a switcher that lets you
switch to video mode, choose a model,
choose duration, write a prompt —
and of course the important thing is
that you can templatize this too.
You can create a scenario
where the model walks into a scene, turns around,
exits — just like in a real product page video.
And that goes into the template too.
[In response to a question about production time for video:]
I think part of what makes it fast
comes from the system itself.
A big part of the work was done beforehand —
all the items were already in the system,
all the models too.
The Total Look was already ready in the system,
and all that remained was composing them into a scene.
The scene itself was built before the video.
You can see it on the website already.
That concept — the hot air balloon,
that scene — all happened before the video,
even before the client asked for video.
Then it was very easy to say:
now we're ready for video.
That's the whole build-up we do here.
We go from the most basic —
the studio lookbook, very clean with the models —
up to campaign
and editorial, all the way to video.
The system is meant
to cover everything —
and all of it needs
to be built on that foundation.
This can also take just minutes —
what I uploaded yesterday was twenty minutes of work —
I created images and sent them off.
We'll end here.
Thank you all so much — it was great to meet you
and to connect.
Take care of yourselves. Bye bye.